Episode 48
Execution
JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game
The Culling Game Part 1
So, is Mai-chan dead?
It's the clan head you
should be concerned about.
Besides, the one who's nearly dead is Maki.
That so? Good thing, that.
Maki-chan's a real beauty, but she's no good.
She can't support a man.
Any woman who can't walk
humbly behind her man
deserves to be stabbed
in the back and killed.
Mai-chan's a great woman in that regard.
Special First-Grade Sorcerer    Naoya Zen'in
She has the same face and
the same tits as Maki-chan.
She may put on a brave face,
but she understands her place as a woman.
You're late.
What were you doing?
Your own father is in critical condition!
Sorry.
But what's it matter if I'm here or not?
I'm gonna be the next head
of the Zen'in Clan anyway.
All my older brothers are knuckleheads.
And Uncle,
you're his little brother,
but you're lackluster.
Your daughters are out of the question.
And Jinichi-kun, well...
Your looks are no good.
Woulda been better if you
got Toji-kun's looks.
Special First-Grade Sorcerer    Ogi Zen'in
Special First-Grade Sorcerer    Jinichi Zen'in
Papa's in critical condition, y'know?
Cut me some slack.
I see everyone's here.
Just now, the head of the Zen'in Clan,
Naobito Zen'in-sama, has passed away.
I, Furudate, shall now read his will,
which he entrusted to me.
It was Naobito-sama's wish that
this will be read by me once
Ogi Zen'in-sama,
Jinichi Zen'in-sama,
and Naoya Zen'in-sama
were all gathered together.
If there are no objections,
then I shall begin the reading of his will.
First, Naoya Zen'in shall be made
the 27th head of the Zen'in Clan.
Second, Naoya shall inherit all
the assets and cursed tools stored
in both the Jujutsu High and
the Zen'in Clan's forbidden vaults,
and Naoya shall require agreement
from either Ogi Zen'in or Jinichi Zen'in
to make use of their contents.
Tsk.
Well, that's fine.
However,
in the event that Satoru Gojo has died,
or otherwise lost the use of his
mental faculties for any reason,
then the covenant with
Toji Fushiguro shall be fulfilled.
Megumi Fushiguro shall be
welcomed into the Zen'in Clan,
and that same person shall
become the head of the Zen'in Clan,
inheriting all of its assets.
Huh?!
This ain't good.
Those two have no balls.
They think having some
unknown brat as the head
would be better than me,
so they ain't doing jack.
Where's Megumi-kun, and
what's he doing right now?
I don't know much...
Only that he's on a mission
to find Yuji Itadori in Tokyo.
Who's that?
The vessel of Sukuna.
Then go tell the big shots
that Naoya Zen'in is gonna
kill Sukuna's vessel.
Megumi-kun is with Sukuna's vessel, yeah?
I'll kill 'em both together.
Tokyo is pandemonium right now.
People can die anytime for any reason there.
Once I kill him, the rest
will work itself out.
I'm the head of the Zen'in Clan!
Die!
Kugisaki!
Only me!
You take it from here.
Die!
Itadori.
Itadori-kun.
What will you do?
Yuji.
How are your injuries?
They're fine, other than where
I took that Black Flash.
It's probably because of Sukuna.
I can feel how his power has grown stronger.
Yuji.
Don't worry about me.
You can return to Jujutsu High, you know.
I'd like to retrieve the remains
of Shoso and the others, too.
I'm not worried.
It's not even an issue of
me wanting to return or not.
Sukuna is plotting something
that uses Fushiguro.
Plus, I've killed so many people.
What are you going to do when someone
you saved kills someone else in the future?
I can't stay with the others anymore.
And are you okay with this, Choso?
I killed your little brothers, too.
It's fine.
That was an accident.
Eso and Kechizu would have
done the same in my position.
Forgiving you or not doesn't matter.
That's what it means to be siblings.
Let's go.
For now, we need to reduce
the number of cursed spirits.
Choso!
Yuji.
How terrifying.
I already sensed he was
powerful when we fought.
Now he's added subtlety to it.
He has unfaltering control
of his cursed energy
and exceptional physical strength.
He's truly like a war god!
That shows he wasn't yet
in top shape until now.
You're impressive, my little brother.
You're still saying that?
I'll say it as often as it takes.
Remember back.
They should have been there.
Your father should have had
stitches in his forehead, too.
Megumi-kun ain't here?
Am I the first to arrive?
Is that really possible?
He's way too slow.
Who's this guy?
Was he just talking about Fushiguro?
What are y'all doing, anyway?
You're sticking out too much.
Not gonna try to escape?
Escape?
What, you don't know?
You've been sentenced to death.
You lost Satoru-kun's protection, after all.
Huh?!
There are many sorcerers who've been saved
due to Gojo-san's influence,
pride, and whims.
My business is with Megumi-kun,
so to be blunt, I couldn't
care less if you live or die.
Don't want you running
around willy-nilly, though,
so I'm gonna break your legs for now.
What do you want with Fushiguro?
I need him to die.
Though it'd be great for me if he'd
write a few lines before he goes.
I heard Megumi-kun's been searching for you.
He's certainly fast, but something's off.
It's probably his technique.
You're doing better than I expected.
I honestly underestimated you.
I know the vessel's got stuff going on,
but what's that thing beside him?
Guess I'll crank the speed up a bit more.
Gojo-sensei?! No!
It's even creepier!
Huh? You're not alone.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Who are you?
Whoever he is, his goal is...
What are each of you to Itadori-kun?
So you are here to execute Yuji.
Hold up. I'm on your side.
You're Okkotsu-kun, yeah?
Okkotsu!
The second-year Fushiguro mentioned!
A special-grade sorcerer, like Gojo-sensei!
And you are?
I'm Naoya Zen'in.
I'm Maki-chan's cousin,
and I've been told to kill
Itadori-kun, like you were.
We're running, Yuji.
So relax.
I'll stay outta your way.
The blond one's a speed type
with some kind of trick.
We need to avoid getting into a chase.
I'll stall him.
Will you be okay?
In return, once you've killed Itadori-kun,
could you hold off on reporting it for a bit?
I want to use him as bait
so I can see someone.
I will be.
You're the one they're after, Yuji.
That black-haired one...
Okkotsu. Just worry about
getting away from him.
He seems like the same type as Satoru Gojo.
You'll die if you fight him.
I shoulda kept quiet about Megumi-kun.
That gave me shivers.
It's a plan that keeps Yuji
from fighting another human
and prevents him from
feeling guilty toward me.
He's such a handful.
We'll meet up at yesterday's spot!
Fine by me.
I'll leave that one to you, then.
Yeah!
He's fast!
He's this fast with a drawn sword?!
He's fast.
I'd planned to crush him
when he broke into a run.
Tsk!
I was trying to block Okkotsu's path,
but he read my intentions!
I was watching earlier.
That's Blood Manipulation, isn't it?
I don't know why you have it, though.
Still, it's not that scary,
aside from Piercing Blood.
And producing Piercing
Blood takes Convergence.
There's a long build-up.
I don't need to say any more, do I?
It's checkmate. You're gonna die.
You're the one who'll die.
Did you think you could
go after my little brother
and leave here alive?
I'm sure I cut him, too.
He's like Maki-san.
Surprised?
I don't seem like the power type, do I?
Even without raw power,
he has an insane amount of cursed energy!
I actually am on the weaker side.
He's enhancing himself with cursed
energy to cover for his lack of power.
Everyone does that to some degree,
but when he does it...
The exact opposite of me, then.
Have you noticed?
I have even more cursed
energy than Gojo-sensei.
But Sensei has his Six Eyes,
so he wastes practically no energy
when activating his technique.
He's the best there is when
it comes to performance.
I can run out of cursed energy,
but Sensei can't.
Enough chatting.
Shit!
The better the sorcerer,
the harder it is to read the
flow of their cursed energy.
For a different reason from why yours is.
Third-rate
When a sorcerer is inexperienced with manipulating cursed energy, there's a deviation in the
cursed energy during their preliminary movements, allowing the prediction of their next action.
That's because the better a sorcerer is,
the more precisely they
manipulate cursed energy.
When they have mastered manipulating cursed energy, there is no such deviation in their cursed energy, making it difficult to predict their action until the last second.
First-rate
That means you can't predict
their attack until the last second.
But with this guy...
There's cursed energy constantly rising
from his entire body, even his sword!
It's not even a question
of reading his movements!
All of his attacks can
prove to be decisive blows,
and he can reduce all damage
to the bare minimum!
You take it from here.
Sorry, but I can't afford to die yet!
There are some types
who center their training
around the use of a weapon,
but you don't want to become
dependent on a cursed tool
and neglect your manipulation
of cursed energy.
That's still a ways off for you, though.
So Slaughter Demon's just
an emergency measure.
You never taught me that!
You're putting too much focus into the blade.
It broke?
Well, of course it would.
He's one of Gojo-sensei's students.
I guess you won't go down easily.
The wound's deep!
But none of my organs are falling out!
And now we're both unarmed!
I can win this!
What are you doing?
We're just playing, Rika-chan.
"Rika"?! What is this thing?!
A shikigami?!
Where did it come from?!
Hold him still.
I can't move!
What power!
I'm sorry,
Itadori-kun.
Older brothers who are less competent
than a younger brother serve no purpose.
...I can't understand how you
could never love your brothers.
...please report Itadori-kun's death...
...all of the distortions may
have started back then.
Don't look down on me!
So start by saving me...
It's checkmate.
Next Episode
One More Time
Tsumiki has been drawn into this game, too.